<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<root>

  <collection title="News">

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Simon Adkins</h2> is playing Don Lockwood in Singin' in the Rain, Upstairs at the Gatehouse.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>John Alastair</h2> recently filmed on The Wrong Man's 2.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Ruth Alfie Adams</h2> most recently played Brenda in Stratford East production of Fins Ain't Wot They Used To Be.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Stephane Anelli</h2> recently completed his reprisal of the leading role of Cosmo in the Singin' in the Rain UK Tour and Japan.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Simon Anthony</h2> is Jimmy in the very well received production of White Christmas at West Yorkshire Playhouse.]]>
      </text>
    </news>



<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Audrey Ardington</h2> will be seen in the feature film London Road.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Jenni Banerjee</h2> recently filmed The Secret Lives for Talkback Finland playing Katariina Mäkelä.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

    <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Suzy Bastone</h2> plays Tiffany in the feature film Monochrome.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

    <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Gareth Berliner</h2> can be seen in Coronation Street as the semi regular Macca.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

    <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Matt Blair</h2> plays Mr Drayton in Suffragette due for release 2015.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

    <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Kieran Brown</h2> is currently in Phantom of the Opera and has played the Phantom several times this year.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

    <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Wendy Mae Brown</h2> is shooting on Man Down 2 following her recent success playing Oda Mae Brown in the UK Tour of Ghost.]]>
      </text>
    </news>


    <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Phillip Browne</h2> is back from a very successful period performing globally on luxury liners.]]>
      </text>
    </news>


  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Nick Butcher</h2> has reprised his role in Barnum previously at Chichester Festival Theatre for the UK Tour.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Criselda Cabitac</h2> was recently seen in the Gala Concert Performance of Miss Saigon and can currently be seen in the film The Paranormal Diaries.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Claire Cage</h2> played the defence barrister in the trial storyline in 7 episodes of Coronation Street and recently filmed Holby as her character of Natalie Fletcher from the sister programme Casualty.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Stefano Cassetti</h2> filmed on the German feature film Outside the Box.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Heather Chasen</h2>  can be seen in the award winning feature film Les Misérables.]]>
      </text>
    </news>



  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Ellie Chidzey</h2> can be seen in the feature film The Right Juice playing the female lead role of Sally.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Flaminia Cinque</h2> has just completed filming Suspicion for the Discovery Channel and the radio play Victory directed by Richard Eyre.]]>
      </text>
    </news>


  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Charlie Clapham</h2> appears in Kickass 2 and continues as wonderful regular, Freddie, in Hollyoaks.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Anna Marie Cseh</h2> filmed in Paolo Sorrentino's Youth and her short film Skin is being well received on the festival circuit.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Fo Cullen</h2>  was most recently seen in  2 episodes of the TV drama, Line of Duty.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Lex Daniel</h2> was seen in 24: Live Another Day.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

    <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Victoria Donovan</h2> plays Vicky in  Who Needs Enemies released on DVD.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

    <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Eileen Dunwoodie</h2> filmed on Ghostwriter for FFP New Media.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

 <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Peter Hamilton Dyer</h2> is in rehearsals at Shakespeare's Globe for The Changeling and The Broken Heart.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Manal El-Feitury</h2> will soon be rehearsing for Streets the Musical prior to which she was in Exhibit B at the Barbican.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Brett Fancy</h2> shot the feature film Untitled and has been voicing a new Computer Game.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

    <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Francesca Fenech</h2> was recently seen in Our Town at the Almeida following her run as Tracey in Hairspray at the Gordon Craig Theatre.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Daniel Fletcher</h2> reprised his role of Denis Dupree in Rock of Ages UK Tour and then climbed Mount Kilimanjaro for charity.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Jye Frasca</h2> recently filmed on Galavant and has acquired his Green Card.]]>
      </text>
    </news>


  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Pooja Ghai</h2> was recently the assistant director for the Infidel at Stratford East.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
      <![CDATA[<h2>Jennie Goossens</h2> most recently seen at the Jermyn Street Theatre in Flowers of the Forest.]]>
      </text>
    </news>



<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Tina Gray</h2> seen in a recent episode of Doctors, is currently in rehearsals for 2 theatre productions, The Pier & The Singing Stones.]]>
      </text>
    </news>


<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Simon Green</h2> filmed an episode of Mr Selfridge and was recently seen in 24: LIve Another Day.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>John Hales</h2> was nominated in the BAFTA Breakthrough Brits and continues developing various writing projects of his own and comissioned work.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Douglas Hansell</h2> is currently performing in the Wharf Review for the Sydney Theatre Company.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Lesley Harcourt</h2> was seen at The Edinburgh Festival in the productions This is Ceilidh (you may have been lucky to catch the West End performances of this) and The Collector, which subsequently transferred to The Arcola Theatre.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Elizabeth Healey</h2> will commence filming on Caden in the New Year.]]>
      </text>
    </news>


  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Simon Hepworth</h2> was seen in several episodes  EastEnders, filmed on Tulips and shortly commences rehearsals for the title role in King Lear for the Guildford Shakespeare Company.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Rendah Heywood</h2> recently workshopped a new production Mrs Assad and Me.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Joan Hodges</h2> filmed on Pompidou! for the BBC. ]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Daniel Hope</h2> can be seen in Wicked in the ensemble with a Boq cover. ]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Amy Howerska</h2> has booked many of her tour dates for her Stand Up for 2015. ]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Simon Hubbard</h2> recently completed filming series 8 of George Gently in which he plays regular PC Taylor. ]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Cameron Jack</h2> recently filmed on Silent Witness.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Edmund Kente</h2> recently filmed the pilot of Knifeman, as well as episodes of Mr Selfridge, Downton Abbey and Vicious.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Mark Killeen</h2> most recently completed filming on Clavius opposite Joseph Fiennes and is heavily featured in Street Fighter: Assassin's Fist recently lauched on DVD.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Daniel Kobbina</h2> was in the National Theatre production Hotel and has just completed filming on the next series of Science of Stupid.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Daniel Koek</h2> has recently launched his second album High following his successful year playing Jean Valjean in Les Misérables.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Akira Koieyama</h2> is filming on location for Strikeback and is one of the leads in Street Fighter: Assassin's Fist recently released on DVD.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Haruka Kuroda</h2> has completed filming on her third series of Officially Amazing and she can currently be seen in Usagi Yojimbo at Southwark Playhouse.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Joshua Lacey</h2> was most recently seen alongside Martin Freeman in Richard III.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Frances Leak</h2> has recently graduated from Guildford School of Acting.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Tom Lister</h2> can be seen in the very well received UK Tour of Calamity Jane playing Wild Bill Hickock and continues in his charity work for Hope for Justice.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Sion Lloyd</h2> is playing Abanazar at the Belgrade Theatre Coventry.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

      <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Andy Mace</h2> is currently playing the walking cover of Scar and Pumba in the West End production of The Lion King.]]>
      </text>
     </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Amy Marchant</h2> can currently be seen in Shakespeare In Love at the Noel Coward Theatre.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Gavin Marshall</h2> was recently seen in the production Letters Home for Grid Iron in Edinburgh.]]>
      </text>
    </news>
<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Eliza McClelland</h2> was recently seen in Noises Off and The Late Edwina Black at Suffolk Theatre.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Sarah Moss</h2> is playing the title role in Conderella at Colchester Theatre.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Kay Murphy</h2> can be seen in the RSC's award winning production of Matilda playing the role of Mrs Wormwood.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Lucy Newman-Williams</h2> recorded the radio show The Awakening for Women's Hour.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Benjamin Noble</h2> is the writer and producer of The Outside In which has been successful on the festival circuit.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>John O'Dowd</h2> is celebrating winning best sitcom with the rest of the cast and crew of Moone Boy at the British Comedy Awards.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Owen O'Neill</h2> has booked several tour dates for his stand up gigs.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Mercy Ojelade</h2> was most recently seen at The Royal Court in their 10 line plays event.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

    <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Mateo Oxley</h2> was a member of Soho Theatre's Young Playwrights Actors Company.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Dharmesh Patel</h2> was most recently seen in the Bush Theatre's production of Albion.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>David Peart</h2> recently filmed on Mission Impossible 5 and Mr Selfridge and was seen at The Bush Theatre's production of Mary & Frank.]]>
      </text>
    </news>


  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Jason Pennycooke</h2> can be seen at The Shaftesbury Theatre playing Bobby in the production Memphis.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

      <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Lauran Rae</h2> is playing Inanna in Aladdin at Cambridge Arts Theatre prior to which she was in Hairspray in Macau.]]>
      </text>
      </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Katie Ray</h2> recently returned from a Seabourn cruise where she was a principle vocallist.]]>
      </text>
    </news>


  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Michael Riseley</h2> is playing Montparnasse in Les Misérables at the Queens Theatre.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>George Rossi</h2> has recently been seen on our screens as a guest lead in daytime drama Doctors.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

<news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Ethan Rouse</h2> is the voice of Peter in the animated series Mike the Knight.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Joseph Rye</h2> is rehearsing for the Finborough Theatre's production of Pig Girl.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

   <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Sean Sloan</h2> is about to start rehearsals for God of Carnage at the MAC Belfast.]]>
      </text>
      </news>

   <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Kiruna Stamell</h2> is currently reprising her role of Wendy in the National Theatre's production of Great Britain at the Haymarket Theatre, and will appear in the Christmas episode of Holby City.]]>
      </text>
      </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Sam Spiegel</h2> recently filmed on the feature film The Honourable Rebel.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Marvin Springer</h2> was most recently seen in Porgy & Bess at the Open Air Theatre Regents Park, prior to which he was in Sunny Afternoon at Hampstead Theatre.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Colin Starkey</h2> recently filmed the feature film A Slight Trick of the Mind playing Dr Watson and a guest lead in an episode of Holby City.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Bradley Taylor</h2> filmed the short film Out.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Natalie Taylor Gray</h2> is currently a vocalist on the Oceania Riveria liner.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Oliver Thornton</h2> currently playing  Arthur in Camelot at the Two River Theatre in New York City.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Sara Topham</h2> recently completed the run of Love Me Do at The Palace Theatre Watford.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Sadao Ueda</h2> recently filmed feature London Has Fallen and for TV productions, I Live With Models and Vicious.]]>
      </text>
    </news>



  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Steve Varnom</h2> filmed on the feature film God the Father.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Oliver Watton</h2> currently playing Jack in Jack and the Beanstalk in Yeovil and was recently seen in a guest role of Casualty.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Anna-Marie Wayne</h2> is currently touring with War of the Worlds.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Anne Wittman</h2> recently filmed an episode of Suspicion for the Discovery Channel.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  <news>
      <date> </date>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[<h2>Emma Woods</h2> is the choreographer of Cinderella at Basildon Theatre.]]>
      </text>
    </news>

  </collection>
</root>
